A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, National Affairs, Program Subject Files FA578
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, National Affairs, Program Subject Files
1971-1972
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA578
1.2 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Approved Action Programs, 1971 (Box 1)
- Approved Program Actions, 1971 (Box 1)
- Boston Solid Waste Project -- Rashomon in Roxbury, 1971 (Box 1)
- University of California (Berkeley), 1971 (Box 1)
- CEDCO & Capital Formation Inc (CFI), 1972 (Box 1)
- Cooperative Assistance Fund (CAF), 1972 (Box 1)
- Bedford-Stuyvesant Re-Assessment Evaluation, [1972] (Box 1)
- Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration and Redevelopment Re-Assessment, [1972] (Box 1)
- Fund for the City of New York, 1972 (Box 1)
- John Jay College, 1972 (Box 1)
- Labor Research and Education, University of California -- Brendon Sexton, 1971 (Box 1)
- Los Angeles Technical Service, 1972 (Box 1)
- University of Montreal School of Criminology, 1972 (Box 1)
- National Area Development Institute, 1972 (Box 1)
- National Center for Voluntary Action, 1972 (Box 1)
- National Council for Voluntary Action, 1972 (Box 1)
- National Farm Workers Service Center, 1972 (Box 1)
- National Municipal League, 1971 (Box 1)